Guide to the Confederate Imprint collection, 1855-1879 MS 071
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series III: Crandall Numbers; 1855-1867, 227678
  - Pollard, Edward A. The Second Year of the War, 1863; 227920 (Box 12, Folder C2650)
  - Pollard, Edward Alfred. Seven Days' Battles in Front of Richmond, 1862; 227919 (Box 12, Folder C2652)
  - Warder, T.B. The Battle of Young's Branch 156p., 1862; 227918 (Box 12, Folder C2662)
  - Warren, Kittrell J. History of the 11th Georgia Vols., 1863; 227917 (Box 12, Folder C2663)
  - Fremnatle. Three Months in the Southern States, 1864; 227916 (Box 12, Folder C2670)
  - Stranger's Guide and Official Directory, Richmond, 1863; 227915 (Box 12, Folder C2677)
  - Bilbo, Com. W.N. Past, Present, and Future... Confederacy, 1861; 227914 (Box 12, Folder C2692)
  - Brown, Albert Gallatin. State of the Country. Speech of Hon. A.G. Brown of Mississippi in the Confederate Senate, December 24, 1863; 227913 (Box 12, Folder C2697)
  - Convention of Cotton Planters Proceedings, 1861; 227912 (Box 12, Folder C2720)
  - Dahlgrem, Charles G. Letter to... Gn.Harris... State Rights, 1861; 227911 (Box 12, Folder C2724)
  - DJarnette, Daniel C. The Monroe Doctrine. Speech of Hon. D.C. De Jarnette of Virginia, in the Confederate House of Representatives, pending negotiations for peace, January 30, 1865; 227910 (Box 12, Folder C2728)
  - Delchamps, J.J. Looking Brothers. Spiced Stew., 1863; 227909 (Box 12, Folder C2730)
  - Electoral Election Ticket, November 6, 1861; 227908 (Box 12, Folder C2744)
  - Fuller, Hiram. The Times! or the Flag of Truce 18p., 1865; 227907 (Box 12, Folder C2746)
  - Grayson, N.J. Reply to Prof. Hodge on "The State of the Country" 32p., 1861; 227906 (Box 12, Folder C2760)
  - Green, Duff. Tracts and Suggestions, 1864; 227905 (Box 12, Folder C2763)
  - Henry, Gustavus Adolphus. Speech, 1864; 227904 (Box 12, Folder C2767)
  - Lamar, L.Q.C. Speech (photocopy), 1864; 227903 (Box 12, Folder C2780)
  - MacMahon, T.W. Cause and Contrast: An Essay on the American Crisis 192p., 1862; 227902 (Box 12, Folder C2784)
  - MacQueen, John Frazier. Chief Points in the Laws or War and Neutrality 102p., 1863; 227901 (Box 12, Folder C2785)
  - Moore, S. McD. Substance of a Speech, 1861; 227900 (Box 12, Folder C2789)
  - Northrop, Claudian B. Political Remarks, 1861; 227899 (Box 12, Folder C2795)
  - Pollard, Edward A. Southern Spy, 1862; 227898 (Box 12, Folder C2825)
  - Richardson, George W. Speech of George W. Richardson of Hanover in Committee of the Whole, on the report of the Committee on Federal Relations in the Convention of Virginia, April 4, 1861, 1862; 227897 (Box 12, Folder C2831)
  - Segar, Joseph E. Speech to House of Delegates in Virginia 23p., March 30, 1861; 227896 (Box 12, Folder C2840)
  - Stuart, Alexander H.H. To the People of Augusta County Broadside (photocopy), 1861?; 227895 (Box 12, Folder C2851)
  - Summers, George W. Speech... on Federal Relations, 1861; 227894 (Box 12, Folder C2852)
  - Thornwell, James H. Our Danger, 1862; 227893 (Box 12, Folder C2859)
  - Thomwell, J.H. State of the Country, 1861; 227892 (Box 12, Folder C2861)
  - Treason in Virginia. Broadside (photocopy), 1861; 227891 (Box 12, Folder C2867)
  - Tucker, John Randolph. The Southern Church Justified... 35p., May 21, 1863; 227890 (Box 12, Folder C2870)
  - Virginia Electoral Ticket, 1861; 227889 (Box 12, Folder C2874)
  - Wiley, C.H. Scriptural Views of National Trials or The True Road to the Independence and Peace of the Confederate States of America, 1863; 227888 (Box 12, Folder C2877)
  - Jones, Charles C. Religious Instruction of the Negroes, 1861; 227887 (Box 12, Folder C2888)
  - Miles, James W. Relation Between the Races, 1861; 227886 (Box 12, Folder C2890)
  - Verot, A. Esclavage and Abolitionisme, 1862; 227885 (Box 12, Folder C2894)
  - Confederate Receipt Book (photocopy), 1863; 227884 (Box 12, Folder C2906)
  - Jones, Joseph. Agricultural Resources of Georgia. Address before the Cotton Planters Convention of Georgia at Macon, December 13, 1860, 1861; 227883 (Box 12, Folder C2918)
  - Southern Telegraph Companies. Report to Postmaster General, 1862; 227882 (Box 12, Folder C2942)
  - Raleigh and Gaston Railroad Company. Proceedings of Fourteenth Annual Meeting of the Stockholders of the Raleigh and Gaston Railroad Company with repots[sic] of the president, treasurer and co., 1864; 227881 (Box 12, Folder C2992)
  - Chisolm, Julian J. A Manual of Military Surgery for the Use of Surgeons in the Confederate States Army, 1862; 227880 (Box 12, Folder C3028)
  - Goffres, Joseph Marie. Illustrated System of Bandaging, 1864; 227879 (Box 12, Folder C3031)
  - Gross, Samuel David. A Manual of Military Surgery (Wallpaper Covers), 1862; 227878 (Box 12, Folder C3033)
  - Macleod, George H.B. Notes on the Surgery of the War in the Crimea with Remarks on the Treatment of Gunshot Wounds, 1862; 227877 (Box 12, Folder C3036)
  - Porcher, Francis Peyre. Resources of the Southern Fields and Forests, Medical, Economical, and Agricultural. Being Also a Medical Botany of the Confederate States, 1863; 227876 (Box 12, Folder C3041)
  - Warren, Edward. An Epitome of Practical Surgery, for Field and Hospital, 1863; 227875 (Box 13, Folder C3044)
  - Map of Virginia, 1862; 227874 (Box 13, Folder C3066)
  - Maxwell, Mary Elizabeth. John Marchmont's Legacy. A Novel. By Miss M.E.Bradden, 1865; 227873 (Box 13, Folder C3075)
  - The British Partiza n, 1864; 227872 (Box 13, Folder C3082)
  - Hugo, Victor. Les Miserables (pt.1,2,4,5), 1863; 227871 (Box 13, Folder C3096)
  - Leigh, Ella. Confessions... (photocopy), 1865; 227870 (Box 13, Folder C3100)
  - Longstreet, Augustus Baldwin. Master William Mitten, 1864; 227869 (Box 13, Folder C3101)
  - McCabe, James D. Aide-de-Camp, 1863; 227868 (Box 13, Folder C3104)
  - Duncan, Blauton. Dissolving Views of Richmond (photocopy), 1862?; 227867 (Box 13, Folder C3122)
  - Dunn, George and Company. Collection of Comic and Sentimental Valentines (photocopy), 1863; 227866 (Box 13, Folder C3123)
  - Boys and Girls Stories of the War, 1863?; 227865 (Box 13, Folder C3126)
  - Macleod, Norman. Wee Davie, 1864; 227864 (Box 13, Folder C3130)
  - Temple, Neville and Edward Trevor. Tannhauser or The Battle of the Bards. A poem, 1863; 227863 (Box 13, Folder C3138)
  - Randall, James Ryder. Maryland, my Maryland (photocopy), 1862; 227862 (Box 13, Folder C3151)
  - Libby Prison Minstrels Broadside (photocopy), 1863; 227861 (Box 13, Folder C3243)
  - New Year's Dinner to Gen'l Lees Army (photocopy), 1864; 227860 (Box 13, Folder C3246)
  - Branson, Thomas A. The Jack Morgan Songster 64p., 1864; 227859 (Box 13, Folder C3256)
  - Burrowes, John F. Burrowes' Pianoforte Primer, n.d.; 227858 (Box 13, Folder C3257)
  - Hopkins, John. Hopkins' New Orleans Song Book, n.d.; 227857 (Box 13, Folder C3260)
  - Moore, Miranda. Songs of Love and Liberty 62p., 1864; 227856 (Box 13, Folder C3263)
  - Southern Soldier's Prize Songster, n.d.; 227855 (Box 13, Folder C3272)
  - Dunnavaut, William W. To the Members of the Confederate Congress. [requesting the office of public printer and enclosing circular of Ritchie and Dunnavaut, June 1, 1861; 227854 (Box 13, Folder C3277)
  - Carrie Bell, A ballad, n.d.; 227853 (Box 13, Folder C3368)
  - The Exotics: Flowers of Song, n.d.; 227852 (Box 13, Folder C3439)
  - First Love Waltz, n.d.; 227851 (Box 13, Folder C3457)
  - Freedom's Muster Drum, n.d.; 227850 (Box 13, Folder C3468)
  - God Save the Southern Land, 227849 (Box 13, Folder C3510)
  - Awake! A Southern War Song, n.d.; 227848 (Box 13, Folder C3521)
  - Her Bright Smile Haunts Me Still, n.d.; 227847 (Box 13, Folder C3528)
  - Blackmar Collection of Standard Music, 227846 (Box 13, Folder C3533)
  - The March of the Southern Men, n.d.; 227845 (Box 13, Folder C3634)
  - Georgia Musical Album, n.d.; 227844 (Box 13, Folder C3693)
  - On Guard!, n.d.; 227843 (Box 13, Folder C3712)
  - The Prisoner's Lament, n.d.; 227842 (Box 13, Folder C3757)
  - Spring Time Polka, n.d.; 227841 (Box 13, Folder C3850)
  - The Standard Bearer, 227840 (Box 13, Folder C3851)
  - There's Life in the Old Land Yet, 227839 (Box 13, Folder C3888)
  - The Musical Olio, n.d.; 227838 (Box 13, Folder C3909)
  - War to the Yankee! Song of the Confederates (photocopy), 1861; 227837 (Box 13, Folder C3937)
  - When This Cruel War is Over, n.d.; 227836 (Box 13, Folder C3961)
  - When This Cruel War is Over!, n.d.; 227835 (Box 13, Folder C3962)
  - Who Will Care for Mother Now, n.d.; 227834 (Box 13, Folder C3968)
  - The Musical Olio, n.d.; 227833 (Box 13, Folder C3938)
  - Address to the People of North Carolina. Signed by 12 North Carolinian educators at a Conference of teachers and other friends of educations held in Raleigh, 1861?; 227832 (Box 13, Folder C3984)
  - Bigham, Wm. A Grammar of the Latin Language for the Use of Schools with Exercises and Vocabularies, 1863; 227831 (Box 13, Folder C4029)
  - Branson, L. First Book in Composition Applying the Principles of Grammar to the Art of Composing, 1863; 227830 (Box 13, Folder C4030)
  - Browne, George Y. Browne's Arithmetical tables, combined with easy lessons in mental arithmetic for beginners, 1865; 227829 (Box 13, Folder C4031)
  - Browne, George Y. Browne's Arithmetic Tables 64p., 1865; 227828 (Box 13, Folder C4032)
  - Bingham, Wm. Caesaer's Commentaries on the Gallic War, with a Vocabulary and Notes, 1864; 227827 (Box 13, Folder C4034)
  - Campbell, William A. The Child's First Book. Approved by the Educational Association of Virginia through their Committee, 1864; 227826 (Box 13, Folder C4036)
  - Christison, John. A Grammar of the French Language 143p., 1863; 227825 (Box 13, Folder C4045)
  - Summers, Thos. O. Intellectual Arithmetic upon the Inductive Method of Instruction, 1862; 227824 (Box 13, Folder C4046)
  - Dagg, John L. Grammar of the English Language, 1864; 227823 (Box 13, Folder C4048)
  - The First Confederate Speller, 1861; 227822 (Box 13, Folder C4052)
  - The First Reader for Southern Schools 24p., 1864; 227821 (Box 13, Folder C0453)
  - Illustrated Alphabet (photocopy), 1863?; 227820 (Box 13, Folder C4058)
  - Lander, S. Our Own Primary Arithmetic, 227819 (Box 13, Folder C4060)
  - Lander, S. Our Own School Arithmetic, 1863; 227818 (Box 13, Folder C4061)
  - Moore, Mrs. Marinda Branson. The Dixie Primer Third Edition 32p., 1863; 227817 (Box 13, Folder C4066)
  - Moore, M.B. The Dixie Elementary Spelling Book for the use in Common Schools, 1864; 227816 (Box 13, Folder C4067)
  - Moore, Mrs. Marinda Branson. The First Dixie Reader. 2 copies, 1863; 227815 (Box 13, Folder C4068)
  - Moore, M.B. Geographical Reader for the Dixie Children, 1862; 227814 (Box 13, Folder C4070)
  - Moore, M.B. Primary Geography, Arranged as a Reading Book with Questions and Answers, 1864; 227813 (Box 13, Folder C4071)
  - Rice. John H. A New Descriptive Geography, A System of Modern Geography, compiled from various sources, and adapted to the present condition of the world, expressly for the use of schools and academies in the Confederate States of America, 1862; 227812 (Box 14, Folder C4077)
  - The Confederate Reader: containing selections in Prose and Poetry, 1864; 227811 (Box 14, Folder C4083)
  - Smith, R.M. The Confederate Spelling Book, 1865; 227810 (Box 14, Folder C4086)
  - Smith, Roswell Chamberlain. Louisiana English grammar. Published by order of His Excellency, Henry W. Allen, governor of Louisiana, 1865; 227809 (Box 14, Folder C4087)
  - Smythe, Charles W. Our Own Elementary Grammar, 1863; 227808 (Box 14, Folder C4090)
  - Sterling, Richard and J.D. Campbell. Our Own First Reader for the use of Schools and Families, 227807 (Box 14, Folder C4097)
  - Sterling, Richard and J.D. Campbell. Our Own Second Reader for the Use of Schools and Families, 227806 (Box 14, Folder C4101)
  - Sterling, Richard and J.D. Campbell. Our Own Spelling Book for the Use of Schools and Families, 227805 (Box 14, Folder C4102)
  - Sterling, Richard and J.D. Campbell. Our Own Third Reader for the Use of Schools and Families, 227804 (Box 14, Folder C4105)
  - Stewart, K.J. Geography for Beginners, n.d.; 227803 (Box 14, Folder C4107)
  - Malkev, John. The Palmetto Dictionary, n.d.; 227802 (Box 14, Folder C4113)
  - York, Brantley. York's English Grammar, Revised and Adapted to Southern Schools. Third Edition, 1864; 227801 (Box 14, Folder C4121)
  - Doggett, David Seth. A Nation's Ebenezer. A discourse delivered in the Broad St. Methodist Church, Richmond, Virginia, Thursday, September 18, 1862: the Day of Public Thanksgiving appointed by the President of the Confederate States, 227800 (Box 14, Folder C4136)
  - Elliott, Stephen. Address of the Rt. Rev. Stephen Elliott, D.D., the the thirty-ninth annual convention of the Protestant Episcopal Church, in the Diocese of Georgia, 1861; 227799 (Box 14, Folder C4140)
  - Elliott, Stephen. God's Presence, 1861; 227798 (Box 14, Folder C4146)
  - Elliott, Stephen. New Wine, 1862; 227797 (Box 14, Folder C4149)
  - Elliott, Stephen. Our Cause in Harmony with the Purposes of God in Christ Jesus. A sermon preached in Christ Church, Savannah, on Thursday, September 18th, 1862, being the day set forth by the President of the Confederate States, as a day of prayer and thanksgiving for our manifold victories, and especially for the fields of Manassas and Richmond, Ky., 227796 (Box 14, Folder C4150)
  - Elliott, Stephen. "Samson's Riddle". A Sermon Preached in Christ Church, Savannah 24p., March 27, 1863; 227795 (Box 14, Folder C4151)
  - Elliott, Stephen. "Vain is the Help of Man". A Sermon Preached in Christ Church, Savannah, on Thursday, September 15, 1864, being the day of fasting, humiliation, and prayer appointed by the Governor of the State of Georgia., 227794 (Box 14, Folder C4153)
  - Minnigerode, Charles. Power: A Sermon 20p., November 13, 1864; 227793 (Box 14, Folder C4172)
  - Moore, T.V. Discourse, 1861; 227792 (Box 14, Folder C4173)
  - Palmer, Benjamin Morgan. A Discourse Before the General Assembly of South Carolina 24p., December 10, 1863; 227791 (Box 14, Folder C4175)
  - Paris, John. A Sermon: Preached before Brig.-Gen. Hoke's Brigade 15p. (2 copies-orig. and photocopy), February 28, 1864; 227790 (Box 14, Folder C4177)
  - Pierce, George F. Word of God, 1862; 227789 (Box 14, Folder C4179)
  - Ruffner, W.H. The Oath, 1864; 227788 (Box 14, Folder C4187)
  - Stiles, Joseph Clay. National Rectitude, n.d.; 227787 (Box 14, Folder C4194)
  - Tupper, Henry Allen. A Thanksgiving Discourse (photocopy), 1862; 227786 (Box 14, Folder C4200)
  - The New Testament of the Lord and Saviour Jesus Christ. Published in Augusta by the Confederate States Bible Society, 1862; 227785 (Box 14, Folder C4216)
  - The Book of Common Prayer and Administration of the Sacraments; and other Rites and Ceremonies of the Church in the Confederate States of America, 227784 (Box 14, Folder C4225)
  - McGill, Rt. Rev. John, Faith, the Victory, or a Comprehensive View of the Principal Doctrines of the Christian Religion, 1865; 227783 (Box 14, Folder C4275)
  - Quintard, C.T. Confederate Soldiers' Pocket Manual, 1863; 227782 (Box 14, Folder C4235)
  - Army Hymn Book, 1863; 227781 (Box 14, Folder C4239)
  - Soldier's Hymn Book, 1864; 227780 (Box 14, Folder C4253)
  - The Southern Zion's Songster, n.d.; 227779 (Box 14, Folder C4254)
  - Root, S. Primary Bible Questions for Young Children, 1864; 227778 (Box 14, Folder C4261)
  - Presbyterian Church in the United States. General Assembly. Minutes of the General Assembly of the Presbyterian Church in the Confederate States of America. With an appendix. Vol.I., 1861; 227777 (Box 14, Folder C4478)
  - Presbyterian Church in the United States General Assembly. Minutes of the General Assembly of the Presbyterian Church in the Confederate States of America; with an appendix. Vol.I, 1864; 227776 (Box 14, Folder C4481)
  - Journal of the Proceedings of the General Council of the Protestant Episcopal Church in the Confederate States of America from Nov.12 to Nov.22 1862, 1863; 227775 (Box 14, Folder C4519)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church, Confederate States, Proposed Constitution 60p., 1861; 227774 (Box 14, Folder C4522)
  - Protestant Episcopal Church in the Confederate States of America. Journal of the sixty-eighth annual council of the Protestant Episcopal Church in Virginia, held in St. Paul's Church, Richmond on the 20th, 21st, and 22nd May, 1863, 227773 (Box 14, Folder C4556)
  - ... Advice to soldiers, n.d.; 227772 (Box 14, Folder C4559)
  - Christ's Gracious Invitation 8p., 186-; 227771 (Box 14, Folder C4560)
  - Broaddus, Andrew. Sermon: It Is a Fearful Thing to Live, 227770 (Box 14, Folder C4590)
  - Broadus, John Albert. We Pray for You At Home, n.d.; 227769 (Box 14, Folder C4592)
  - Brockenbrough, Mrs. Frances Blake. A Mother's Parting Words to Her Soldier Boy... Evangelical tract society no.127, 186?; 227768 (Box 14, Folder C4593)
  - Brockenbrough, Mrs. Francis Blake. ... A Mother's Parting Words to her Soldier Boy. (A New Tract for Soldiers, no.18), 186?; 227767 (Box 14, Folder C4594)
  - Buck, William C. A Tract for the Army, n.d.; 227766 (Box 14, Folder C4597)
  - Burrows, John Lansing. The Christian Scholar and Soldier. Memoirs of Louis Minor Coleman, professor in the University of Virginia--Lt.Col.of First Reg't, Va. Artillery, 1864; 227765 (Box 14, Folder C4600)
  - The Christian's Consolation, n.d.; 227764 (Box 14, Folder C4610)
  - Soldier's Tract Assoc. Tract no.75, 1862?; 227763 (Box 14, Folder C4613)
  - Crumly, William H. The Soldier's Bible., n.d.; 227762 (Box 14, Folder C4619)
  - Dagg, J.L. Proclamation of Peace. No.68, n.d.; 227761 (Box 14, Folder C4626)
  - Denison, Mrs. Mary (Andrews). Angel Lilly, 227760 (Box 14, Folder C4632)
  - Do You Love God?, n.d.; 227759 (Box 14, Folder C4635)
  - Do You Want a Friend?, 227758 (Box 14, Folder C4636)
  - Faith in God, n.d.; 227757 (Box 14, Folder C4655)
  - The Feast of Belshazzar and its End, 227756 (Box 14, Folder C4656)
  - Soldiers Tract Assoc. Tract no.63, 1862?; 227755 (Box 14, Folder C4658)
  - Fowler, James H. My Spirit Shall Not Always Strive, n.d.; 227754 (Box 14, Folder C4659)
  - ... Friendly Conversation, 227753 (Box 14, Folder C4660)
  - ... The Gate of Prayer, n.d.; 227752 (Box 14, Folder C4663)
  - Grasty, Rev.Jno.S. A Great Question Asked? no.113, n.d.; 227751 (Box 14, Folder C4672-3)
  - Grasty, John Marshall. A Noble Testimony, n.d.; 227750 (Box 14, Folder C4674)
  - ...Hearing or Hardening, n.d.; 227749 (Box 14, Folder C4687)
  - Heber, Reginald. Noah's Carpenters, n.d.; 227748 (Box 14, Folder C4689)
  - Hunns, Henry. From "English Hearts and Hands", 227747 (Box 14, Folder C4690)
  - Hoge, William James. The Improvident Traveller, n.d.; 227746 (Box 14, Folder C4697)
  - Hoge, William James. What Wilt Thou That I Should Do?, n.d.; 227745 (Box 14, Folder C4698)
  - ...How Israel was Delivered from Two Cruel Invasions, n.d.; 227744 (Box 15, Folder C4704)
  - Howard, Rev.Wm. Wilt Thou Be Made Whole? no.112, n.d.; 227743 (Box 15, Folder C4706)
  - (printed as one item) No. 49 "In the Enemy's Lines" and No.50 "Things to Think Of", 227742 (Box 15, Folder C4714 and C4889)
  - Jeter, Jeremiah Bell. The Evils of Gaming..., n.d.; 227741 (Box 15, Folder C4723)
  - Keeling, Henry. The Colporteur's Commission, n.d.; 227740 (Box 15, Folder C4727)
  - Kinsbury, Rev. Theodore B. The Great Amnesty. No.97, n.d.; 227739 (Box 15, Folder C4730)
  - The Last Time. At Head of Title: No.71, 186-; 227738 (Box 15, Folder C4732)
  - ...The Life Preserver, n.d.; 227737 (Box 15, Folder C4737)
  - ...Lovest Thou Me?, n.d.; 227736 (Box 15, Folder C4743)
  - McIntosh, William H. How Long Have I to Live?, n.d.; 227735 (Box 15, Folder C4747)
  - Soldiers' Tract Assoc. Tract no.68, 1862?; 227734 (Box 15, Folder C4748)
  - Mangum, Adolphus Williamson. The Holy Shield... no.96, 186?; 227733 (Box 15, Folder C4751)
  - Martin, Rev.J.H. Come Thou With Us, and We Will Do Thee Good no.71, 227732 (Box 15, Folder C4757)
  - Moore, Thomas Verner... What Can I Do?, n.d.; 227731 (Box 15, Folder C4764)
  - More, Hannah. Parley the Porter..., n.d.; 227730 (Box 15, Folder C4766)
  - Soldiers Tract Assoc. Tract No.79, 1862?; 227729 (Box 15, Folder C4785)
  - Page, Harlan. Motives to Early Piety, n.d.; 227728 (Box 15, Folder C4788)
  - ... Paget And "Tall George", 227727 (Box 15, Folder C4789)
  - Soldiers' Tract Association Tract no.4, 1862?; 227726 (Box 15, Folder C4797)
  - Pharr, Walter H. A Short History of the Life, Character, and Death of Capt. John B. Andrews, 227725 (Box 15, Folder C4798)
  - ...The Precious Blood of Christ, of How a Soldier Was Saved, n.d.; 227724 (Box 15, Folder C4805)
  - ...Prepare for Battle, n.d.; 227723 (Box 15, Folder C4807)
  - Pressense, Edmond de. The French Soldier, 227722 (Box 15, Folder C4809)
  - Proctor, J.A. A Tract for the Soldier, n.d.; 227721 (Box 15, Folder C4813)
  - Soldier's Tract Assoc. Tract no.49, 1862?; 227720 (Box 15, Folder C4814)
  - Soldier's Tract Assoc. Tract no.73, 1862?; 227719 (Box 15, Folder C4823)
  - Soldier's Tract Assoc. Tract no.72, 1862?; 227718 (Box 15, Folder C4824)
  - ..."Ruinous Consequences of Gambling", n.d.; 227717 (Box 15, Folder C4830)
  - ...Scripture illustrations of the all-sufficiency of Christ, n.d.; 227716 (Box 15, Folder C4840)
  - ...The Sentinel, n.d.; 227715 (Box 15, Folder C4843)
  - Sewell, Mrs. Our Father's Care. A Ballad, n.d.; 227714 (Box 15, Folder C4845)
  - Shiloh. A Sermon., n.d.; 227713 (Box 15, Folder C4849)
  - Shuck, Rev.L.H. "Home Sweet Home" No.74, n.d.; 227712 (Box 15, Folder C4851)
  - Sir Henry Havelock, n.d.; 227711 (Box 15, Folder C4856)
  - Sir Henry Havelock. The Christian Soldier., n.d.; 227710 (Box 15, Folder C4857)
  - The Soldier. An Affecting Narrative of Facts, n.d.; 227709 (Box 15, Folder C4862)
  - Soldiers' Tract Association Tract No.65, 1862; 227708 (Box 15, Folder C4869)
  - Teasdoll, T.C. The Season of Divine Mercy, n.d.; 227707 (Box 15, Folder C4885)
  - Soldiers' Tract Association Tract No.74, 1862?; 227706 (Box 15, Folder C4899)
  - ...A Voice from the Australia, n.d.; 227705 (Box 15, Folder C4904)
  - What is it to Believe in Christ? No.93, n.d.; 227704 (Box 15, Folder C4917)
  - ... Where are the Christians in the Army?, n.d.; 227703 (Box 15, Folder C4920)
  - Where Are You Going?, n.d.; 227702 (Box 15, Folder C4921)
  - Whitfield, Theodore. The Danger of Delay No.101, n.d.; 227701 (Box 15, Folder C4924)
  - Whither Bound?, 227700 (Box 15, Folder C4925)
  - ...Why Sit Ye Here Idle? no.94, n.d.; 227699 (Box 15, Folder C4930)
  - Wengate, W.M. I Have Brought My Little Brother Back, n.d.; 227698 (Box 15, Folder C4934)
  - Wingate, W.M.... I Have Brought My Little Brother Back no.70, 186?; 227697 (Box 15, Folder C4935)
  - Georgia Relief and Hospital Association Report, 1862; 227696 (Box 15, Folder C4964)
  - Confederate States Almanac for 1863, 1862; 227695 (Box 15, Folder C4989)
  - Confederate States Almanac for 1864. Calculations made at University of Alabama, 1863; 227694 (Box 15, Folder C4996)
  - Confederate States of America Almanac, 1865; 227693 (Box 15, Folder C4997)
  - Richardson's Almanac..., 1862; 227692 (Box 15, Folder C5033)
  - Richardson's Virginia and North Carolina Almanac for the year of our Lord 1864, 1863; 227691 (Box 15, Folder C5044)
  - Freemasons. Virginia. Grand Lodge. Free Masonry and the Wars. Report of the Committee under the Resolutions of 1862, Grand Lodge of Virginia, in reference to our relations as Masonic bodies and so Masons, in the North and South, growing out of the manner in which the present war has been prosecuted. Adopted by the Grand Lodge of Virginia, December 12, 1864, and ordered to be published. John Dove, Grand Secretary, 1865; 227690 (Box 15, Folder C5102)
  - Freemasons. Virginia, Richmond Lodge No.10. By-Laws and List of Members..., 1864; 227689 (Box 15, Folder C5112)